Instead of looking in every video app
to find a movie or TV show,
use OneGuide and see them together.
OneGuide has app channels that show you
what’s available in each video app.
Browse your favorite app channels, and discover new ones.
When you find one you like,
mark it as a favorite by selecting the star next to the name.
To add more, select App channels in the navigation bar.
Your favorite app channels are listed here,
and also more video apps you can explore.
More app channels brings you to the full browse list,
You can easily dive into your favorite app channels too.
Select an app name to browse the channels from that app.
If OneGuide is in your Most Recently Used list on Home,
you can jump straight to your
favorite app channels from there.
Discover more! Get information and tips from Xbox Help.